<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<!-- This is a sample XML file displayed when the user hasn't specified any quotes.  -->
<Quotes>
<Quote>
  <Text>He asked me if I knew what time it was.  I said, "Yes, but not right now."</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I've been doing a lot of abstract painting lately, extremely abstract.  No brush, no paint, no canvas, I just think about it.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>You can't have everything.  Where would you put it?</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I went to this restaurant last night that was set up like a big buffet in the shape of an Ouija board.  You'd think about what kind of food you want, and the table would move across the floor to it.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I went to a general store.  They wouldn't let me buy anything specifically.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I went down the street to the 24-hour grocery.  When I got there, the guy was locking the front door.  I said, "Hey, the sign says you're open 24 hours."  He said, "Yes, but not in a row."</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>When I go shopping, I love to freak out salespeople.  They ask me if they can help me and I say, "Have you got anything I'd like?"  Then they ask me what size I need and I say, "Extra medium."</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I went to the hardware store and bought some used paint.  It was in the shape of a house.  I also bought some batteries, but they weren't included so I had to buy them again.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I bought my brother some gift-wrap for Christmas.  I took it to the Gift Wrap Department and told them to wrap it, but in a different print so he would know when to stop unwrapping.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>Friday, I was in a bookstore and I started talking to a French-looking girl.  She was a bilingual illiterate —she couldn't read in two different languages.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>Last week I bought a new phone.  I took it out of the box, hooked it up to the wall.  Pressed redial.  The phone had a nervous breakdown.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I bought a self-learning record to learn Spanish.  I turned it on and went to sleep; the record got stuck.  The next day I could only stutter in Spanish.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I went down to the store and bought some blank cassette tapes. When I got home I put one in my cassette deck and turned it up full blast.  I was walking around my house when I heard a knock on my door.  It was my neighbor complaining about the noise.  He's a mime.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I'm writing a book.  I've got the page numbers done, so now I just have to fill in the rest.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I'm writing an unauthorized autobiography.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I just got out of the hospital.  I was in a speed reading accident —I crashed into a bookmark.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I have a decaffeinated coffee table.  You'd never know it to look at it.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>One time a cop pulled me over for running a stop sign.
He said, "Didn't you see the stop sign?"
I said, "Yeah, but I don't believe everything I read."</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>There's a fine line between fishing and standing on the shore looking like an idiot.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>A friend of mine is into Voodoo Acupuncture.  You don't have to	go.  You'll just be walking down the street, and...Ooooohhhhhh, that feels better...</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I hate it when my foot falls asleep during the day because that means it's going to be up all night.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>When I woke up this morning my girlfriend asked me, "Did you sleep well?"
I said, "No, I made a few mistakes."</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I was once arrested for walking in someone else's sleep.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>Some people are afraid of heights.  Not me, I'm afraid of widths.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>Last year I went fishing with Salvador Dali.  He was using a dotted line.  He caught every other fish.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>When I was a little kid we had a sand box.  It was a quicksand box.  I was an only child.  Eventually.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I don't know how she did it but my girlfriend got poison ivy on her brain and the only way she can scratch it is if she thinks about sandpaper.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>After they make styrofoam, what do they ship it in?</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I saw a subliminal advertising executive, but only for a second.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I have two very rare photographs.  One is a picture of Houdini locking his keys in his car.  The other is a photograph of Norman Rockwell beating up a child.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I stayed up all night playing poker with Tarot cards.  I got a full house and four people died.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>George is a radio announcer, and when he walks under a bridge, you can't hear him talk.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I had some eyeglasses.  I was walking down the street when suddenly the prescription ran out.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>When my kid turned two I was really anxious, because he'd doubled his age in a year.  I thought, if this keeps up, by the time he's six he'll be ninety.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I had fried octopus last night.  You have to be really quiet when you eat it, otherwise it emits a cloud of black smoke and falls on the floor.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>You know how it is when you go to be the subject of a psychology experiment and nobody else shows up and you think maybe that's part of the experiment?  I'm like that all the time.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>A metaphor is like a simile.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>Every day, the hummingbird eats its own weight in food.  You may wonder how it weighs the food.  It doesn't —it just eats another hummingbird.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I listen to the police band on my CB radio.  Once I dialed 911 and dedicated a crime to my girlfriend.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
<Quote>
  <Text>I daydreamed that I was falling and just before I hit the ground, I fell asleep.</Text>
  <Attribution>Steven Wright</Attribution>
</Quote>
</Quotes>
